[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Brian, the hyperactive and irritating waiter in the movie Office Space, worked at which restaurant?", "correct_answer": "Chotchkies", "incorrect_answers": ["Flingers", "Ruby Tuesdays", "T. G. I. Fridays"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Godzilla has a star on the Hollywood Walk of Fame.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Approximately what percentage of the water of the Niagara River flows over the Horseshoe Falls?", "correct_answer": "90%", "incorrect_answers": ["70%", "50%", "10%"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what movie did Jennifer Aniston star alongside Jim Carrey as his girlfriend Grace?", "correct_answer": "Bruce Almighty", "incorrect_answers": ["The Cable Guy", "Man on the Moon", "Ace Ventura: When Nature Calls"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which two elements comprise the bulk of the atmosphere of Neptune?", "correct_answer": "Hydrogen and Helium", "incorrect_answers": ["Hydrogen and Methane", "Helium and Carbon Dioxide", "Helium and Methane"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the James Bond movies starred Pierce Brosnan and was released in 1997?", "correct_answer": "Tomorrow Never Dies", "incorrect_answers": ["GoldenEye", "The World is Not Enough", "Die Another Day"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Boise City, Oklahoma was the only city within the continental United States to be bombed during World War II.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the closest definition of Santeria?", "correct_answer": "A Cuban based religion popular in Lousiana.", "incorrect_answers": ["Another name for the Catholic Church in Lousiana.", "Another name for the Protestant Baptists religion in Lousiana.", "A Jewish based religion popular in Lousiana."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In \u201cScream\u201d, what were the words that Billy spoke right before shooting Randy and revealing himself as one of the killers?", "correct_answer": "We all go a little mad sometimes.", "incorrect_answers": ["Boy, do I have a surprise for you!", "I told you I have a surprise for you.", "Surprise, Sidney!"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which would be found at 39 degrees 43 minutes North latitude?", "correct_answer": "The majority of the Mason-Dixon Line.", "incorrect_answers": ["The Tropic of Cancer", "The Tropic of Capricorn", "The border between Canada and  Washington State."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the world of design and construction, what is Zodiaq?", "correct_answer": "A material used for countertops", "incorrect_answers": ["A material for improving safety glass", "An underlayer for granite", "A product for wall insulation"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Nadia Wayans did not appear in the1988 movie Im Gonna Get You Sucka with her siblings.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}]